<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Homepage on Emma Johnston Counselling &amp; Psychotherapy</title><link>https://emma.vaines.org/</link><description>Recent content in Homepage on Emma Johnston Counselling &amp; Psychotherapy</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 12:00:00 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://emma.vaines.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How Does Therapy Work?</title><link>https://emma.vaines.org/services/how-does-therapy-work/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 12:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://emma.vaines.org/services/how-does-therapy-work/</guid><description>“When a person realises he has been deeply heard, his eyes moisten. I think in some real sense he is weeping for joy. It is as though he were saying, &amp;ldquo;Thank God, somebody heard me. Someone knows what it&amp;rsquo;s like to be me.” Carl R. Rogers
I believe the work we do together is co-created and each client gets a unique experience.
I love the image of this forest path, and it reminds me of how protected I&amp;rsquo;ve always felt whilst being amongst trees.</description></item><item><title>Fees &amp; Locations</title><link>https://emma.vaines.org/services/fees-and-locations/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 12:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://emma.vaines.org/services/fees-and-locations/</guid><description>Fees My fees take into account the robust training I have undertaken to become qualified so far as well as my professional experience, the cost of room hire, insurance and professional supervision and insurance on a monthly basis.
As a member of both the British Association of Counselling and Psychotherapy (BACP) and The UK Association of Transactional Analysts (UKATA). I make a commitment to myself and my clients to ensure my knowledge and expertise is continually developing and up to date.</description></item><item><title>Emma Johnston</title><link>https://emma.vaines.org/about/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 12:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://emma.vaines.org/about/</guid><description>My clients have always really valued my honesty and my no nonsense down to earth approach. I am not about therapeutic tricks and gimmicks - I believe that long standing change happens in the safety of a strong therapeutic relationship. With that in mind I offer you my unique self and sense of humour with warmth and acceptance.
I am a wife, mum and step mum. I have had a varied career before retraining to become a therapist.</description></item><item><title>Emma Johnston Dip Couns MBACP</title><link>https://emma.vaines.org/contact/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 17:01:34 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://emma.vaines.org/contact/</guid><description>Contact me today to book an initial consultation and discuss how we might work together during counselling sessions.
Address: UK Counselling Network C.I.C 209-211 Wakefield Rd, Drighlington, Bradford BD11 1EB</description></item></channel></rss>